A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Constituent, 2002-2006., Extent: 10.7 cu. ft. (Box 59-89.)
  - 2003
    - #2161443 - 2161458, June. (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - #2161460 - 2161521, June. (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - #2161524 - 2161788, June. (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - #2161848 - 2162371, June. (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - #2163051 - 2164569, June. (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - #2164803 - 2166433, June. (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - #2166623 - 2167230, June. (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - #2167615 - 2168677, June. (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - #2168737 - 2169112, June. (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - #2169191 - 2171070, June. (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - #2171131 - 2173125, June - July. (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - #2173132 - 2175044, July. (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - #2175162 - 2175874, July. (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - #2176500 - 2177654, July. (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - #2178157 - 2179168, July. (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - #2179244 - 2179914, July. (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - #2180450 - 2182510, July. (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - #2182573 - 2187839, July - August. (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - #2188359 - 2190162, August. (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - #2190226 - 2191249, August. (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - #2191268 - 2193351, August. (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - #2193352 - 2194749, August. (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - #2195868 - 2197255, August. (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - #2197735 - 2198625, August - September. (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - #2199695 - 2201480, September. (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - #2201739 - 2202658, September. (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - #2203884 - 2204519, September. (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - #2205157 - 2208309, September. (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - #2208310 - 2209292, September - October. (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - #2209321 - 2212622, October. (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - #2213064 - 2214616, October. (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - #2214861 - 2217060, October. (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - #2217059 - 2219405, October. (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - #2219500 - 2220506, October. (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - #2220740 - 2223405, October - November. (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - #2223884 - 2224893, November. (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - #2224915 - 2226875, November. (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - #2226987 - 2227993, November. (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - #2228267 - 2229448, November. (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - #2229736 - 2230406, October - November. (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - #2230411 - 2230852, November. (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - #2231170 - 2233725, November - December. (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - #2233735 - 2234475, November - December. (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - #2234676 - 2236699, December. (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - #2236702 - 2236858, December. (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - #2237156 - 2237222, December. (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - #2237223 - 2238314, December. (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - #2238425 - 2238760, December. (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - #2239637 - 2241057, December. (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - #2241493 - 2242467, December. (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - #2242572 - 2243021, December. (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - #2243037 - 2243990, December. (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - #2243992 - 2244755, December. (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - F.Y.I. File. (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - 2004
    - #2246438 - 2248543, January. (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - #2248546 - 2250281, January. (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - #2250830 - 2251629, January. (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - #2251727 - 2253628, January. (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - #2253688 - 2255003, January. (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - #2255007 - 2256035, January. (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - #2256084 - 2257364, January. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - #2257384 - 2258096, January - February. (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - #2258110 - 2259164, February. (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - #2259244 - 2260331, February. (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - #2260392 - 2260705, February. (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - #2260784 - 2261666, February. (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - #2261807 - 2262470, February. (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - #2262471 - 2262771, February. (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - #2262785 - 2263044, February. (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - #2263072 - 2263650, February. (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - #2264048 - 2264745, February. (Box 77, Folder 13)
    - #2264748 - 2265008, February. (Box 77, Folder 14)
    - #2265025 - 2265224, February. (Box 77, Folder 15)
    - #2265232 - 2266053, February. (Box 77, Folder 16)
    - #2266428 - 2266632, February. (Box 77, Folder 17)
    - #2266633 - 2267487, February. (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - #2267618 - 2267949, February. (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - #2268031 - 2268468, February. (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - #2269005 - 2269953, February - March. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - #2270071 - 2271779, March. (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - #2272149 - 2272761, March. (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - #2272770 - 2273212, March. (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - #2273213 - 2273751, March. (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - #2273768 - 2275628, March. (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - #2275914 - 2279079, March. (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - #2280157 - 2283528, March. (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - #2282306 - 2285695, March. (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - #2285840 - 2288679, March - April. (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - #2288978 - 2290927, April. (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - #2290961 - 2292239, April. (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - #2292241 - 2294562, April. (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - #2294940 - 2296705, April. (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - #2296710 - 2296934, April - May. (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - #2297018 - 2299983, May. (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - #2300025 - 2301285, May. (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - #2301893 - 2303043, May. (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - #2303906 - 2305332, May. (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - #2305603 - 2307688, May. (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - #2307819 - 2309025, May. (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - #2309027 - 2309870, May. (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - #2310025 - 2310439, May - June. (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - #2310495 - 2311170, June. (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - #2311467 - 2313599, June. (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - #2313600 - 2315728, June. (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - #2316027 - 2317754, June. (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - #2318006 - 2318335, June. (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - #2320435 - 2321889, June - July. (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - #2322330 - 2322600, June - July. (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - #2322609 - 2324004, June - July. (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - #2323987 - 2324734, July. (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - #2325065 - 2326709, July. (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - #2327110 - 2329908, July. (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - #2330139 - 2334288, July. (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - #2334527 - 2336459, July - August. (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - #2336471 - 2337499, August. (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - #2337910 - 2338861, August. (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - #2338886 - 2340920, August. (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - #2341021 - 2342080, August. (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - #2342383 - 2343370, August. (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - #2343404 - 2343782, August. (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - #2343783 - 2345642, August. (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - #2346262 - 2346967, August. (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - #2347432 - 2349548, September. (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - #2349762 - 2351623, September. (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - #2351698 - 2353362, September. (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - #2353601 - 2356366, September. (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - #2356406 - 2357722, September - October. (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - #2358221 - 2359204, September - October. (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - #2359444 - 2360337, September - October. (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - #2360519 - 2362404, October. (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - #2363389 - 2364111, October. (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - #2364114 - 2364576, October. (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - #2364874 - 2366041, October. (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - #2366476 - 2366655, October. (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - #2367077 - 2367202, October. (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - #2367325 - 2368418, October. (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - #2368476 - 2369017, October. (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - #2369018 - 2369395, October. (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - #2369398 - 2369711, October. (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - #2370516 - 2370937, October - November. (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - #2370938 - 2371938, October - November. (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - #2371973 - 2373170, November. (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - #2373519 - 2374100, November. (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - #2374101 - 2375395, November. (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - #2375819 - 2377171, November. (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - #2377726 - 2379505, November. (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - #2379510 - 2381081, November - December. (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - #2381246 - 2382727, November - December. (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - #2382996 - 2384168, December. (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - #2384170 - 2384510, December. (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - #2384511 - 2385036, December. (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - #2385040 - 2385813, December. (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - #2385914 - 2386343, December. (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - #2386587 - 2387649, December. (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - #2387651 - 2388386, December. (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - #2388388 - 2390005, December. (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - #2390085 - 2390827, December. (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - #2391259 - 2391725, December. (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - 2005
    - #2382964 - 2393292, January. (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - #2393318 - 2393962, January. (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - #2394171 - 2394752, January. (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - #2394771 - 2396220, January. (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - #2396228 - 2398221, January. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - #2398222 - 2399112, January. (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - #2400208 - 2401214, January. (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - #2401217 - 2402100, January. (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - #2402117 - 2403585, January. (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - #2403775 - 2405496, January - February. (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - #2405519 - 2408581, January - February. (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - #2408745 - 2410532, February. (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - #2410997 - 2411764, February. (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - #2411844 - 2415151, February. (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - #2415525 - 2417569, February - March. (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - #2417573 - 2418972, February - March. (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - #2419047 - 2420117, March. (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - #2420593 - 2421547, March. (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - #2422010 - 2423056, March. (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - #2423085 - 2425171, March. (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - #2425749 - 2427548, March. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - #2427567 - 2428236, March. (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - #2428325 - 2429663, March. (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - #2430259 - 2431040, March - April. (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - #2431201 - 2432047, March. (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - #2432069 - 2433004, March - April. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - #2433531 - 2435892, March - April. (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - #2436244 - 2438490, April. (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - #2438500 - 2440140, April. (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - #2441424 - 2443352, April. (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - #2443802 - 2445501, April. (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - #2445718 - 2447138, April - May. (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - #2447147 - 2448185, May. (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - #2448310 - 2448989, May. (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - #2449479 - 2451219, May. (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - #2451225 - 2451419, May. (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - #2451477 - 2453396, May. (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - #2454259 - 2454616, May. (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - #2454622 - 2456237, May. (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - #2456267 - 2457136, May. (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - #2457143 - 2457518, May. (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - #2457551 - 2458155, May. (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - #2458156 - 2458600, May - June. (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - #2458658 - 2459898, June. (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - #2460188 - 2463180, June. (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - #2463183 - 2464118, June. (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - #2464285 - 2465743, June. (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - #2466026 - 2466984, June. (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - #2466985 - 2467450, June. (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - #2468107 - 2469721, June. (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - #2469732 - 2469990, June. (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - #2470074 - 2470981, June. (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - #2472095 - 2472933, July. (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - #2473276 - 2473785, July. (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - #2473805 - 2475222, July. (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - #2475243 - 2475772, July. (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - #2475773 - 2476755, July. (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - #2476914 - 2478324, July. (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - #2478639 - 2481062, July. (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - #2481092 - 2482468, July. (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - #2482520 - 2483320, August. (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - #2483331 - 2484575, August. (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - #2484616 - 2486039, August. (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - #2486274 - 2488180, August. (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - #2488359 - 2489656, August. (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - #2489756 - 2491270, August. (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - #2491735 - 2492654, August. (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - #2492994 - 2493608, August. (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - #2493869 - 2494422, August. (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - #2494434 - 2494937, September. (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - #2494939 - 2496155, September. (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - #2496177 - 2496504, September. (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - #2496556 - 2498116, September. (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - #2498163 - 2499222, September. (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - #2499225 - 2499841, September. (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - #2500408 - 2501196, September. (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - #2501287 - 2502149, September. (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - #2502327 - 2503422, September. (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - #2503424 - 2504693, September. (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - #2504960 - 2505480, September - October. (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - #2505516 - 2507039, October. (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - #2508823 - 2509100, October. (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - #2509303 - 2510948, October. (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - #2510957 - 2513355, October. (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - #2513446 - 2514048, October. (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - #2514063 - 2555762, October. (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - #2555825 - 2556826, October. (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - #2556852 - 2557184, November. (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - #2557474 - 2557892, November. (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - #2557927 - 2558432, November. (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - #2558435 - 2559134, November. (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - #2559145 - 2559387, November. (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - #2559475 - 2559969, December. (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - #2560044 - 2560329, December. (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - #2560330 - 2560373, December. (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - #2560388 - 2561016, December. (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - #2561023 - 2561553, December. (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - #2561554 - 2561568, December. (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - #2561602 - 2561837, December. (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - #2561849 - 2563970, December. (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - #2564645 - 2565487, December. (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Unnumbered Letters, December 2005 - January 2006 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Proclamations and Recognition Requests (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Series V. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Secretary W. Tayloe Murphy, Jr., 1997-2006., Extent: 6.1 cu. ft. (Box 90-107.)
    Contains correspondence and supporting documents that originated or were collected by W. Tayloe Murphy, Jr. during his tenure as Secretary of Natural Resources. The correspondence and documents in this series pertain to many of the Secretariat's agencies and boards, as well as to general natural resources related subjects. Notable files include budget material, the governor's office correspondence and legislators' correspondence, as well as Secretary Murphy's reading files. The reading files contain mostly constituent correspondence responses. Other files of note include the Governor-related files which feature information on meetings and events attended by the Secretary in place of the Governor, as well as information on meetings between the Governor and Secretary Murphy. The Department of Transportation folders contain information on the hotly contested Route 29 Bypass in Charlottesville, and the Environmental Organizations folders contain general information on agencies that worked closely with the Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources.
    Secretary Murphy's correspondence and documents are arranged alphabetically by subject or form. The Reading Files are arranged chronologically, but within each year the documents are arranged in reverse chronological order. (Accessions 42294 and 42398).
    - Budget, 2001. (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 2002. (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Budget, 2002. (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Budget, 2003. (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 2004. (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Budget--FY2006 Agency Narrative Justification Forms, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Budget--FY2006 Agency Narrative Justification Forms, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Budget--FY2006 Agency Narrative Justification Forms, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - Budget--FY2006 Agency Narrative Justification Forms, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Budget--FY2006 Agency Narrative Justification Forms, 2005. (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2001. (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2002. (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2002. (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2003. (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2004. (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Chesapeake Bay Foundation--Expedition Chesapeake, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Conservation Easement Working Group, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence--Congressional, 2002. (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence--Congressional, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence--Congressional, 2003. (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence--Congressional, 2004. (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence--Congressional, 2005. (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (From), 2002. (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (From), 2002-2004. (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (From), 2005. (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (To), 2002. (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (To), 2002. (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (To), 2002. (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (To), 2002-2003. (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence--Governor's Office (To), 2004-2005. (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2002. (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2002. (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2002. (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2003. (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2003. (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2003. (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2003. (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2003. (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence--Legislators, 2004-2005. (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous, 2003-2005. (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous, 2005. (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous, 2005. (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence--Miscellaneous, 2005. (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Organizations--Audubon Society, 2002. (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Organizations--Conservation Fund, 2002. (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Organizations--Environmental Roundtable, 2002. (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Organizations--Piedmont Environmental Council, 2002-2003. (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Organizations--Piedmont Environmental Council, 2002-2003. (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Environmental Organizations--Scenic Virginia, 2002-2005. (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Organizations--Sierra Club, 2002-2004. (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Organizations--Southern Environmental Law Center, 2002-2004. (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Environmental Organizations--Southern Environmental Law Center, 2002-2004. (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Environmental Organizations--Trust for Public Land, 2002. (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Organizations--Valley Conservation Council, 2001-2002. (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Conservation Network, 2002-2005. (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Economic Developers Association, 2002. (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Environmental Endowment, 1999-2003. (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Environmental Endowment, 1999-2003. (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia League of Conservation Voters, 2001-2003. (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia League of Conservation Voters, 2001-2003. (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia League of Conservation Voters, 2001-2003. (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Living Museum, 2003-2005. (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Manufacturers Association, 2000-2003. (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Manufacturers Association, 2000-2003. (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Municipal League, 2004. (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Environmental Organizations--Virginia Petroleum Council, 2003. (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Forestry, Department of, 2002-2004. (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Forestry, Department of, 2002-2004. (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Forestry, Department of, 2002-2004. (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Freedom of Information Act, 2002-2004. (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - GAO Chesapeake Bay Restoration Review, 2005. (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - GAO Chesapeake Bay Restoration Review, 2005. (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Governor-Related Files--Briefing for Governor-Elect Warner and the Cabinet, 2001. (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Governor-Related Files--Briefing for Governor-Elect Warner and the Cabinet, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Governor-Related Files--Briefing for Governor-Elect Warner and the Cabinet, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Governor-Related Files--Governor's Schedule and Meeting Requests, 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Governor-Related Files--Governor's Schedule and Meeting Requests, 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Governor-Related Files--Governor's Schedule and Meeting Requests, 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Governor-Related Files--National Governors Association, 2002. (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Governor-Related Files--National Governors Association, 2002. (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Governor-Related Files--National Governors Association, 2002. (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Governor-Related Files--"One Virginia, One Future" (Warner's Economic Development Strategic Plan), 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Governor-Related Files--"One Virginia, One Future" (Warner's Economic Development Strategic Plan), 2002-2003. (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Governor-Related Files--Southern Governors Association, 2002. (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Governor-Related Files--Warner 2001 Natural Resources Briefing Papers, 2001. (Box 96, Folder 1)